A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Civic Interests, Series D FA313
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Political Organizations
  - Political Organizations - Political Contributions
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 207)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 208)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Pardee, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 209)
    - Political Contributions - Winthrop Rockefeller, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 210)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1951 (Box 29, Folder 211)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 212)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 213)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 214)
    - Political Contributions - General, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 215)
    - Political Contributions - General, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 215A)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1952 (Box 30, Folder 216)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 217)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 218)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 219)
    - Political Contributions - Winthrop Rockefeller, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 220)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Pardee, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 221)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 222)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 223)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 224)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 225)
    - Political Contributions - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 226)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 227)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 228)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 228A)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Mauzé, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 229)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1954 (Box 30, Folder 230)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 231)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 232)
    - Political Contributions - Winthrop Rockefeller, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 233)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 234)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 235)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Mauzé, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 236)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1955 (Box 31, Folder 237)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 238)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 239)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 240)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 241)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1956 (Box 31, Folder 242)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 243)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 244)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 245)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Mauzé, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 246)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 247)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1957 (Box 32, Folder 248)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 249)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 250)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 251)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 252)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1958 (Box 32, Folder 253)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 254)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 255)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 256)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 257)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 257A)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Mauzé, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 258)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1959 (Box 33, Folder 259)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 260)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 261)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 262)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 263)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 263A)
    - Political Contributions - Winthrop Rockefeller, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 264)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Mauzé, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 265)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1960 (Box 33, Folder 266)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 267)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 268)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 269)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 270)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Mauzé, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 271)
    - Political Contributions - Martha Baird Rockefeller, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 272)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 273)
    - Political Contributions - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 273A)
    - Political Contributions - David Rockefeller, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 274)
    - Political Contributions - Laurance Rockefeller, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 275)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Mauzé, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 276)
    - Political Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Mauzé, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 276A)
  - Political Organizations - Republican Organizations - Political Clippings, 1936-1957 (Box 34, Folder 277)
  - Political Organizations - Republican Organizations - Republican Club of 9th Assembly District
    Requests for contributions. Contributions by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. for 15th Assembly District, 9th Assembly District. Refinancing the clubhouse mortgage. Correspondents include Arthur Woods, Robert W. Gumbel, Thomas M. Debevoise, Arthur W. Packard, Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    - Political Organizations - Republican Organizations - Republican Club of 9th Assembly District, 1926-1950 (Box 35, Folder 278)
    - Political Organizations - Republican Organizations - Republican Club of 9th Assembly District, 1926-1950 (Box 35, Folder 278A)
    - Political Organizations - Republican Organizations - Republican Club of 9th Assembly District, 1950-1960 (Box 35, Folder 279)
    - Political Organizations - Republican Organizations - Republican Club of 9th Assembly District, 1950-1960 (Box 35, Folder 279A)
  - Political Organizations - Eisenhower Committees, 1948-1954 (Box 35, Folder 280)
    Appeals for aid to special Eisenhower committees. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Dwight D. Eisenhower exchange of letters on Eisenhower's election as President. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Dwight D. Eisenhower, Abby Rockefeller Mauze, Laurance S. Rockefeller.
  - Political Organizations - Republican Organizations - Maine, 1934-1961 (Box 35, Folder 281)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. made regular campaign contributions to the Republican committees there. Nelson A. Rockefeller made contributions during presidential campaigns. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., L. C. Minor, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
  - Political Organizations - Republican Organizations - Maine, 1934-1961 (Box 35, Folder 0281A)
    David Rockefeller made contributions during presidential campaigns. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
  - Political Organizations - Republican National Finance Committee, 1917-1955 (Box 35, Folder 282)
    Contributions from John D. Rockefeller, Sr. and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Invitations to dinner. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur Woods, Starr J. Murphy, John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Robert W. Gumbel, Robert H. Thayer, Arthur W. Packard.
    128N
  - Political Organizations - Republican National Finance Committee - National Republican Congressional Committee, 1915-1936 (Box 36, Folder 283)
  - Political Organizations - Republican State Committee, 1908-1954 (Box 36, Folder 284)
    John D. Rockefeller, Sr.'s concern over charges that he was buying political influence through contributions to Republican party and publicity on his and John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s donations to Republican organizations. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s regular contributions to Republican State Committee. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, John D. Rockefeller, Sr., John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas M. Debevoise, F. Jamieson.
    128S
  - Political Organizations - Westchester County Republican Committee, 1927-1954 (Box 36, Folder 285)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contributions to committee. Invitations to dinners declined. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas M. Debevoise.
    128W
  - Political Organizations - Westchester County Republican Committee, 1927-1954 (Box 36, Folder 0285A)
  - Political Organizations - Westchester County Republican Committee - Contributions, 1926-1940 (Box 36, Folder 286)
    John D. Rockefeller, Sr., John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller to County committees. Usually $1,000 a year. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Sr., John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas M. Debevoise, Arthur Woods.
  - Political Organizations - Westchester County Republican Committee - Gift Toward Permanent Headquarters, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 287)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Laurance S. Rockefeller contribute to building permanent headquarters for Party in White Plains. Family total was $4,000 out of $100,000 drive. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Laurance S. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Political Organizations - Westchester County Republican Committee - Gift Toward Permanent Headquarters, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 0287A)
    David Rockefeller contributes to building permanent headquarters for Party in White Plains. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
  - Political Organizations - Westchester County Republican Committee - Charles Millard - Campaigns, 1930-1937 (Box 36, Folder 288)
    Ran for Congress urging substitute for 18th Amendment. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. made contributions to his campaigns in 1932, 1934, 1936, also when running for county office. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Charles Millard.
  - Political Organizations - Committee for Constitutional Government - Frank E. Gannett - Gannett Newspapers
    Mr. Gannett headed committee to uphold constitutional government. Anti-New Deal group. Unanswered appeals for contributions, 1937. Gannett for president, no third term movement in 1940, control labor, lower taxes. Pressure group for Bricker Amendment, limitation on income tax. No family interest or participation. Correspondents include Frank Gannett, N. V. Peale, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Sumner Gerard, E. A. Rumely, John E. Lockwood.
    128.1
    - Political Organizations - Committee for Constitutional Government - Frank E. Gannett - Gannett Newspapers, 1937-1950 (Box 36, Folder 289)
    - Political Organizations - Committee for Constitutional Government - Frank E. Gannett - Gannett Newspapers, 1937-1950 (Box 36, Folder 289A)
    - Political Organizations - Committee for Constitutional Government - Frank E. Gannett - Gannett Newspapers, 1951-1960 (Box 36, Folder 290)
    - Political Organizations - Committee for Constitutional Government - Frank E. Gannett - Gannett Newspapers, 1951-1960 (Box 36, Folder 290A)
  - Political Organizations - Committee for Constitutional Government - Guidepost Associates, Inc., 1944-1950 (Box 37, Folder 291)
  - Political Organizations - Suggestions that John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Run for Office, 1938-1946 (Box 37, Folder 292)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. for President, 1940 and 1944. This came from a variety of citizens with mixed motives. Most of the letters came after W. Winchell suggested that the Republican Party was considering John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Nelson A. Rockefeller, Thomas M. Debevoise, H. F. Clark.
    128.2
  - Political Organizations - Wendell Willkie, 1940-1942 (Box 37, Folder 293)
    Support of Willkie's campaign by family. Nelson A. Rockefeller traveled to see Mr. Willkie. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave full-hearted moral support, but did not follow up-with extra contributions. Miscellaneous letters destroyed at office. Correspondents include W. Willkie.
    128.3
  - Political Organizations - Honest Ballot Association, 1912-1948 (Box 37, Folder 294)
    Requests for, reasons for, and qualifications on the gifts made. John D. Rockefeller, Sr. and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. made regular contributions, plus special ones for particular purposes. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Sr., John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy, Willard S. Richardson, E. R. Finch, Talcott Williams.
    128.4
  - Political Organizations - National Republican Builders, Inc., 1933-1941 (Box 37, Folder 295)
    Republican propaganda organization. Thomas M. Debevoise urged against making contributions to it. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. made one small gift in 1933, later requests refused. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s sons did not contribute. Some duplicate letters of appeal destroyed from 1935.
    128.5
  - Political Organizations - National Republican Builders, Inc. - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 37, Folder 296)
  - Political Organizations - National Republican Builders, Inc. - Nelson A. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1938-1941 (Box 37, Folder 297)
  - Political Organizations - National Republican Club, 1934-1959 (Box 37, Folder 298)
    Invitation to John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd to join club, declined. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. pledges $2,000 to save clubhouse. Invitations to dinner declined. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Robert W. Gumbel, Francis A. Jamieson.
    128.6
  - Political Organizations - National Republican Club, 1934-1959 (Box 37, Folder 0298A)
    Invitation to David Rockefeller to join club, declined.
  - Political Organizations - National Republican Club - Nelson A. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 37, Folder 299)
    Invites Nelson A. Rockefeller to join club, dinner invitation, declined.
  - Political Organizations - City Fusion Party, 1933-1951 (Box 37, Folder 300)
    Family interest in good government. Contribution request. Correspondents include Arthur Woods, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Thomas M. Debevoise, Langdon Post, Ben Howe, Miller Brister.
    128.7
  - Political Organizations - City Fusion Party - Contributions, 1933-1937 (Box 37, Folder 301)
    From John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Political Organizations - Proportional Representation Committee, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 302)
    Proposal to repeal proportional representation. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and John D. Rockefeller 3rd asked to join committee against repeal, declined. Not complete. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Arthur Jones.
    128.8
  - Political Organizations - Proportional Representation Committee, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 0302A)
    David Rockefeller asked to join committee against repeal, declined.
  - Political Organizations - Americas Future, Inc., 1943-1960 (Box 38, Folder 303)
    Constitution and Free Enterprise. Request for contributions, declined. Committee for Constitutional Government not supported. Correspondents include Yorke Allen, F. A. Jamieson, Edward T. Hutton.
    128.9
  - Political Organizations - Ralph W. Gwinn - Congressional Reports, 1947-1952 (Box 38, Folder 304)
    Representative sends reports.
    128.10
  - Political Organizations - Committee on National Affairs, 1946-1950 (Box 38, Folder 305)
    Political action committee. Contribution requests, invitations to dinners, declined. Correspondents include Frederick C. McKee.
    128.11
  - Political Organizations - Americans for Democratic Action, 1947-1958 (Box 38, Folder 306)
    Political organization. No contributions made. Correspondents include F. A. Jamieson, Arthur W. Packard, Robert Delson.
    128.12
  - Political Organizations - Americans for Democratic Action, 1947-1958 (Box 38, Folder 0306A)
  - Political Organizations - Barradas League, 1938-1960 (Box 38, Folder 307)
    Activities of League. Reports. Crusader of "scientific capitalism." Ignored by Office.
    128.13
- Russell Sage Foundation
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 1911-1955 (Box 39, Folder 308)
    Information on work of Foundation (including regional planning) sent to Rockefeller office. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas B. Appleget, Robert W. Gumbel.
    142
- Regional Planning Association
  - Regional Planning Association, 1930-1949 (Box 39, Folder 309)
    Davison Fund contributed. Discussions of New York Region's future. Interest of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s sons in planning for City. Contributions were nominal. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions 1930-1934. Award offered to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard, McKim Norton.
    142.1
  - Regional Planning Association, 1930-1949 (Box 39, Folder 0309A)
    Request that David Rockefeller serve on the management group of a study, declined.
  - Regional Planning Association, 1951-1961 (Box 39, Folder 310)
  - Regional Planning Association, 1951-1961 (Box 39, Folder 0310A)
  - Regional Planning Association - Clippings, 1942-1960 (Box 39, Folder 311)
  - Regional Planning Association - Contributions, 1930-1961 (Box 39, Folder 312)
    Listing of payments.
  - Regional Planning Association - Contributions, 1930-1961 (Box 39, Folder 0312A)
  - Regional Planning Association - Meeting Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 313)
  - Regional Planning Association - New York Metropolitan Region Study, 1956-1959 (Box 39, Folder 314)
  - Regional Planning Association - New York Metropolitan Region Study, 1956-1959 (Box 39, Folder 0314A)
- Research
  - Research - Institute for Government Research, 1914-1925 (Box 40, Folder 315)
    Promote efficiency in government. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. $10,000 gift in 1918, 5 year pledge made in 1921, additional publication fund gift made in 1923. Primary interest in budgetary reform, history of Institute. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Raymond B. Fosdick, Jerome D. Greene.
    81
  - Research - Institute for Government Research - Bureau of Public Personnel Administration, 1922-1929 (Box 40, Folder 0315A)
    Sponsored by National Research Council, United States Civil Service, etc. 1922 pledge by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. of $25,000 a year for 3 years. Gift renewed in 1925 for one year, modified to a three year pledge in 1926, renewed for one year in 1928. First contributions were made through Institute, later ones made directly to Bureau. Correspondents include Arthur Woods, Beardsley Ruml, William Gorham Rice.
  - Research - Institute for Government Research - Indian Survey, 1926-1932 (Box 40, Folder 316)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. provides funds for preliminary survey of task. Later underwrites cost of survey up to $125,000. This survey requested by H. Work, Secretary of the Interior. Copy of Study of the Indian Problem. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur Woods.
  - Research - National Budget Committee, 1919-1921 (Box 40, Folder 317)
    Planned program to encourage national budget. John D. Rockefeller, Sr. and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contribute to program. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Raymond B. Fosdick, Willard S. Richardson.
    81.1
  - Research - National Institute for Public Administration, 1914-1932 (Box 40, Folder 318)
    Organization of Institute to take over activities of Training School for Public Services. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution. Dr. Beard's mission to Tokyo. Rural criminal justice survey. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Raymond B. Fosdick, Robert W. Gumbel, Willard S. Richardson, Luther Gulick.
    82.5
    See also Box 2, Folder 10.
  - Research - National Research Council, 1918-1928 (Box 40, Folder 319)
    Sex study, drug study, pure research. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.s contributions. Interest shown in general objectives of Council. Laurance S. Rockefeller gives $1,000 for Pacific Island studies in 1950-1951. Increased gifts in later years. Council interested in conservation, anthropology. John D. Rockefeller 3rd financed expenses of Japanese and Vietnamese scientists to Congress in Manila in 1953. Laurance S. Rockefeller stock gifts to Pacific Science Board. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Raymond B. Fosdick, Laurance S. Rockefeller, H. I. Coolidge.
    81.2
  - Research - National Research Council, 1937-1961 (Box 40, Folder 320)
  - Research - International Auxiliary Language Association, 1920-1958 (Box 41, Folder 321)
    Mrs. Dave Morris's interest in universal secondary language. Request for promotional aid. Esperanto, Interlingua, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s conditional gift. Later requests declined. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, F. G. Cottrell, Alice V. Morris, Arthur Woods, Thomas B. Appleget, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Mrs. J. H. Hammond.
    81.21
  - Research - International Auxiliary Language Association - Printed Material, 1921-1954 (Box 41, Folder 322)
    Articles on common language.
  - Research - Personnel Research Federation, 1924-1935 (Box 41, Folder 323)
    Research in the field of personnel management and relations. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributes to work through Advisory Committee. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas B. Appleget.
    81.4
  - Research - National Academy of Sciences - National Research Endowment, 1926-1927 (Box 41, Folder 324)
    Requests for contribution to aid pure science. Appeal made by H. Hoover, Elihu Root, Charles Evans Hughes. Ultimately declined as not specific enough in purpose and organization. Correspondents include Thomas B. Appleget, Wickliffe Rose, George E. Vincent.
    81.5
- Tarrytown Projects
  - Tarrytown Projects - Tarrytown and North Tarrytown - Miscellaneous
    Variety of small local projects ranging from requests for funds and invitations to dinners to requests for advice and reports on county activities. Many small donations made - community interest. Topics range from schools, bowling, clubs, to politicians and politics. Participation in community projects usually declined. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Jay Downer, Dana S. Creel, Gavriel P. Hayes.
    77
    - Tarrytown Projects - Tarrytown and North Tarrytown - Miscellaneous, 1932-1948 (Box 41, Folder 325)
    - Tarrytown Projects - Tarrytown and North Tarrytown - Miscellaneous, 1932-1948 (Box 41, Folder 325A)
    - Tarrytown Projects - Tarrytown and North Tarrytown - Miscellaneous, 1949-1954 (Box 41, Folder 326)